https://www.bizchair.com/privacy-policy.html

The widest selection of quality furniture at unbeatable prices.
Questions?
We're here to help.
Search Catalog
Thank you! Your submission has been received!
Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.
Log in
Shopping Cart (0)
(0)
Search Catalog
Thank you! Your submission has been received!
Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.
OfficeChairs
The furniture that started it all.
You work hard. Find an office chair that works just as hard for you.
OfficeFurniture
Essentials for wherever you do business.
Our office desks, tables, seating, and supplies are designed to work where you do.
FoldingChairs
Make room for all your guests.
We have the selection you want with the extra space and storage you need.
FoldingTables
Storable surfaces for a larger crowd.
Give yourself, and your guests, extra room for any activity you’re hosting.
ChurchChairs
Welcome visitors with comfortable sanctuary seating.
Chairs in church and Sunday school are a modern way to offer seating to your congregation.
StackChairs
Style and convenience in a chair.
Stack seating enhances your style when in use and is easily stored for extra space.
BarStools
Set the Bar High.
No matter the table, always have the best seat in the house.
RestaurantFurniture
Furniture, kitchen supplies, and restaurant essentials.
Serve your guests an atmosphere that rivals the meals you offer. Great kitchen furniture and essentials set the scene.
SchoolFurniture
Built for a lifetime of learning.
Create an environment designed to optimize learning in all areas of your school.
HomeFurniture
Make yourself at home.
No matter what room of the house, we have home furniture to suit your style.
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is posted to help you understand how BizChair.com collects and processes the information you share when you shop with us.
Please review this Privacy Policy carefully. By browsing our online store, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you would rather we not collect and process information about you, please do not provide it to us and do not access the Site.
1. Disclosure to Third Parties:We will not disclose any personal information to any third party source at any time. All personal information is kept secure and never shared or sold to any third party.
2. Acquisition of Information: We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or otherwise necessary to provide a high level of customer service.
3. Our Employees and Privacy: We train all our employees about the importance of privacy and give access to information about consumers only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.
4. Security Measures: We make access to privacy sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service. We use the highest levels of encryption available for all credit card transactions.
5. Transaction Server: We use external transaction and processing servers to ensure maximum credit card and personal information security.
6. Third-Party Web Beacons: We utilize Google Analytics to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. If you would like more information, see How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps.
We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under 13. Where any such information is inadvertently collected, we will delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us.
We collect the information you share with us, including:
Personal Information: "Personal Information" is information that personally identifies you, like your name, email address and telephone number. We maintain one or more databases to store your Personal Information and may retain it as reasonably required to serve you; and
General Information: When you visit our site, we may collect various categories of general non-personal information "General Information". General Information includes browser, operating system and device information, TCP-IP address and the date, time, length of stay and specific pages accessed during your visits.
Online Identification Tools
Like many ecommerce sites, we use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server to provide a better web experience for our valued customers. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.
We also use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and personalize your experience. A cookie is a small file stored by your internet browser on your computer.
How Your Personal Information is Used, Processed and Disclosed
Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, BizChair does not rent, sell, trade or disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your prior consent. BizChair may, however, use, process and disclose Personal Information to:
send information to you about orders;
fulfill your orders;
process and collect your payments;
customize, analyze, adjust and improve our site to better meet your needs;
enforce BizChair's agreements with you;
prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities; and
comply with potential requests of law enforcement or data protection agencies.
When possible, General Information may be combined and/or linked to Personal Information, in accordance with the purposes specified above.
We may use your General Information and deidentified Personal Information to prepare anonymized, aggregated data about our users ("Anonymized Data"). We may provide third parties with Anonymized Data in describing our site to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for all other lawful purposes. As communicated to third parties, the Anonymized Data does not include any information permitting the recipient to identify, locate or contact you.
Third Party Service Providers
BizChair employs other companies and individuals to perform functions, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, serving ads on our behalf, providing search results and links, and processing credit card payments. These third-party service providers have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions but may not use it for any other purpose.
Retention of Personal Information
BizChair retains Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law.
California Residents
California law permits individuals who provide BizChair with Personal Information and who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please contact us.
Visitors from Outside of the United States
BizChair.com is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting our site from outside the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable US laws. Please note that data protection and other applicable laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those laws or regulations in your country or may otherwise differ from the data protection or consumer protection laws in your country. By using our site, you consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities as described in this Privacy Policy.
Information Security
We have instituted reasonable safeguards to help ensure that information collected is secure. We also take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties who work with us to make the Site (including the software, applications and services provided on the Site) available to you agree to protect personal information that they must access to serve you and to honor your preferences about contacts you receive.
When you send or otherwise transmit your sensitive information (such as your credit card number) to or though BizChair.com, your sensitive information is encrypted and protected with SSL, the current industry-standard encryption protocol. When you are on an SSL-protected page, a picture of a closed lock appears at the bottom or top of some web browsers. Another way to tell if you are on a secure page is to check the URL or address of the page. (Look in the address box or right-click on the page and select "Properties".) These secure SSL-encrypted pages have URLs that start with "https://" instead of "http://".
It is possible for third parties to access information despite our best efforts. Without limiting the terms of our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, you understand that we do not guarantee that your use of the Site and/or information provided by you will be private or secure and we are not responsible or liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the Site. You also understand that any information provided by you or collected by us or our agents in connection with your use of the Site will be used in the manner described above. Please do not use the Site if you do not agree to the terms and conditions described in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices. The modified Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting on our site. Your continued use of our site after the posting of the modified Privacy Policy constitutes your agreement to abide and be bound by it. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you object to any modification, your sole recourse is to stop using our site.
©	2018 BizChair All Rights Reserved.
